{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "garfield",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "blinky",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "gargamel",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "babar",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "disco|stu",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Inspector|Ardilla",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "apu",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "freezer",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|goloso",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "he man",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "oliver|atom",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mickey|mouse",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mario",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "son gohan",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "quique|gavilan",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Kearney",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jefe|Gotier",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Monstruo|Buu",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "astro",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|fortachon",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Puerco|porky",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "dr hibbert",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "El Pato|Donald",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Mark|Lenders",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "milhouse",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pluto",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "lisa|simpson",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "tiro loco|mcgraw",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "akira",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "robotina",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "masha|y el oso",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "maggie|simpson",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "super|sonico",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Joe|quimby ",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "goofy",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "huckleberry|hound",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "la hormiga",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el pajaro|loco",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el inspector",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el fantasma|del espacio",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|vanidoso",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "los gemelos|fantasticos",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "artie|ziff",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Peque√±o Ayudante|de Santa Claus",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "carl|carlson",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "cleto",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "uter",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "edna|krabappel",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "barney",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "patan",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jeremias|springfield",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jessica|Lovejoy",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "kent|brockman",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "kirk|van houten",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Mindy|Simmons",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "montgomery|burns",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "la mujer|maravilla",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "profesor|frink",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Ralph|Wiggum",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "cometin|sonico",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "sam|bigotes",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "leon o",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "astro boy",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "la hormiga|atomica",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el oso|yogi",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jem",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "herbert|powell",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "benito",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "la pantera|rosa",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "funzo",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Richie|Rich",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "duffman",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pikachu",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "lucero|sonico",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jasper",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "battle cat",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jefe|Wiggum",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "super|raton",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jimbo",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Hans|Topo",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "frank|grimes",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "don gato",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|filosofo",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "dr nick",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "birdman",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "vegeta",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "larry|burns",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Luann|Van Houten",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "rayo de|plata",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "lionel|hutz",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "kang",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "krusty",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el gallo|claudio",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "heidi",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el jardinero|willy",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "papa|pitufo",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Ultra|sonico",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mr Croquet",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el inspector|gadget",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "martin|prince",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "hombre|abejorro",
      "pregunta": "101",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el oso|hormiguero",
      "pregunta": "102",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "orko",
      "pregunta": "103",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mcbain",
      "pregunta": "104",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "rayo mcqueen",
      "pregunta": "105",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "rasca",
      "pregunta": "106",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "luiggi",
      "pregunta": "107",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "bugs|bunny",
      "pregunta": "108",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el pato|lucas",
      "pregunta": "109",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "gil",
      "pregunta": "110",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "bart|simpson",
      "pregunta": "111",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Piccolo",
      "pregunta": "112",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Maude|Flanders",
      "pregunta": "113",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "buzz|lightyear",
      "pregunta": "114",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "benji|price",
      "pregunta": "115",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "oficial|matute",
      "pregunta": "116",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "marge|simpson",
      "pregunta": "117",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mate",
      "pregunta": "118",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Otto Mann",
      "pregunta": "119",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "cerebro",
      "pregunta": "120",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "homero|simpson",
      "pregunta": "121",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "flash",
      "pregunta": "122",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pepe le pew",
      "pregunta": "123",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "son goku",
      "pregunta": "124",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "ned|flanders",
      "pregunta": "125",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "scooby|doo",
      "pregunta": "126",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "moe",
      "pregunta": "127",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pinky",
      "pregunta": "128",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "superman",
      "pregunta": "129",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mandibulin",
      "pregunta": "130",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "el coyote",
      "pregunta": "131",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "silvestre",
      "pregunta": "132",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Pica",
      "pregunta": "133",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "mojo",
      "pregunta": "134",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "pablo|marmol",
      "pregunta": "135",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "bobby",
      "pregunta": "136",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "odie",
      "pregunta": "137",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "taz",
      "pregunta": "138",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "baloo",
      "pregunta": "139",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "patty",
      "pregunta": "140",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "bruce|harper",
      "pregunta": "141",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Johnny|Bravo",
      "pregunta": "142",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "shaggy",
      "pregunta": "143",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "marvin",
      "pregunta": "144",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "nelson",
      "pregunta": "145",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "popeye",
      "pregunta": "146",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "lenny",
      "pregunta": "147",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "d'artagnan",
      "pregunta": "148",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "speedy|gonzalez",
      "pregunta": "149",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "lou",
      "pregunta": "150",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Betty|Marmol",
      "pregunta": "151",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Pedro|Picapiedras",
      "pregunta": "152",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Peter|Griffin",
      "pregunta": "153",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "tweety",
      "pregunta": "154",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "jerry",
      "pregunta": "155",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "winnie pooh",
      "pregunta": "156",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "krillin",
      "pregunta": "157",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "dumbo",
      "pregunta": "158",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "poochie",
      "pregunta": "159",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "terri y|sherri",
      "pregunta": "160",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Motita",
      "pregunta": "161",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "seymour|skinner",
      "pregunta": "162",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "superintendente|chalmers",
      "pregunta": "163",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "malefica",
      "pregunta": "164",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "gordo|tony",
      "pregunta": "165",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "selma",
      "pregunta": "166",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Ariel",
      "pregunta": "167",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Helen|Lovejoy",
      "pregunta": "168",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Peter|Pan",
      "pregunta": "169",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Simba",
      "pregunta": "170",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Bob|esponja",
      "pregunta": "171",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Sombras",
      "respuesta": "Pinocho",
      "pregunta": "172",
      "categoria": "sombras"
    }
  ]
}
